A Guide to the Papers of Henry Evans Howell, Jr. 1948-1976
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University Libraries, Old Dominion University
- Political Papers 1948-1973
  - 1969 Gubernatorial Campaign 1969
    - Organization: Students - Directories - Lynchburg College and George Mason College, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 64 Folder 10)
    - Organization: Students - Directories - Christopher Newport College and New River Vo. Tech, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 64 Folder 11)
    - Organization: Students - Directories - ODU, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 64 Folder 12)
    - Organization: Students - Directories (Shenandoah College, UVA Eastern Shore, Va. Intermont College), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 64 Folder 13)
    - Organization: Students - Directories - Virginia State College (Box-folder Box 64 Folder 14)
    - Organization: Students - Directories - William and Mary, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 64 Folder 15)
    - Directories and Catalogues: (Box Box 65)
      Virginia Commonwealth University
      Union Theological Seminary
      University of Richmond
      Longwood College
      John Tyler Community College
      Hampden-Sydney College
      Danville Community College
      Dabney S. Lancaster Community College
      Medical College of Virginia
      William and Mary
      Christopher Newport College
      U.Va. - Eastern Shore
      Hampton Institute
      Virginia Wesleyan College
      Norfolk State College
    - Directories and Catalogues (Box Box 66)
      Virginia Theological Seminary
      Thomas Nelson Community College
      Institute of Textile Technology
      U.Va. Law School
      Virginia Intermont College
      George Mason College
      Mary Washington College
      Marymount College
      University of Virginia
      Southern Seminary Junior College
      Hollins College
      Virginia Western Community College
      VMI
      Bridgewater College
      Eastern Mennonite College
      Washington and Lee
    - Personal Appearances: Young Democrats' Convention, March 29, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 1)
    - Personal Appearances: Meetings with No. Va. Supporters, February - May, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 2)
    - Personal Appearances: Richmond- Black Leaders, May 11, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 3)
    - Personal Appearances: Announcement of Candidacy, June 15,1968; General Correspondence, May-July, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 4)
    - Personal Appearances: Announcement Meeting -Correspondence re: Youth Participation, May-June, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 5)
    - Personal Appearances: Announcement Meeting- Correspondence with "Advance Men," March-June, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 6)
    - Personal Appearances: Stanley Homecoming, July 3, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 7)
    - Personal Appearances: No. Va. Community College - Va. Citizens Consumer Council, July 13, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 8)
    - Personal Appearances: Brunswick Stew- Crewe, July 17, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 9)
    - Personal Appearances: Bricklayers Local- Martinsville, July 20, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 10)
    - Personal Appearances: Virginia Democratic Convention, July 26-27, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 11)
    - Personal Appearances: Richmond Voter Registration Meeting, August 17, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 12)
    - Personal Appearances: Covington Labor Day Rally, September 2, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 13)
    - Personal Appearances: Annandale- No. Va. Supporters,September 4, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 14)
    - Personal Appearances: Richmond- Va. Assoc. of Rescue Squads, September 12, 1968 (Box-folder Box 67 Folder 15)
    - Personal Appearances: Young Democrats Kickoff Dinner, Norfolk, September 14, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 1)
    - Personal Appearances: Richmond- Conflict of Interest Study Commission, September 16, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 2)
    - Personal Appearances: Emporia Peanut Festival, September 28, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 3)
    - Personal Appearances: Hampton- Peninsula Black Leaders, October 10, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 4)
    - Personal Appearances: Va. Medical Political Action Committee, October 13, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 5)
    - Personal Appearances: V.E.A. Convention, October 30 - November 1, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 6)
    - Personal Appearances: Virginia Beach Blacks, November 25, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 7)
    - Personal Appearances: Northern Virginia "Whirlwind Tour," December 3-4, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 8)
    - Personal Appearances: V.A.L.C. Meeting, December 6, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 9)
    - Personal Appearances: Richmond Luncheon, December 7, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 10)
    - Personal Appearances: Richmond, December 10, 1968 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 11)
    - Personal Appearances: Charlottesville, February 1, 1969 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 12)
    - Personnel: Correspondence; Resumes; Notes, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 13)
    - Personnel: Organizational Rosters, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 14)
    - Position Papers: Adult Education Corps- Water Pollution Control, 1969 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 15)
    - Position Papers: Air Pollution- Mental Health, 1969 (Box-folder Box 68 Folder 16)
    - Position Papers: Oceanography and Marine Resources-Misc. Materials, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 1)
    - Position Papers:Drafts on Misc. Topics, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 2)
    - Position Papers: "The Finest of Tomorrow"- Howell Action Program (Copy 1), 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 3)
    - Copy 2 of above (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 4)
    - Public Statements- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 5)
    - Reference - Agriculture in Virginia, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 6)
    - Reference - Arcandria Flood, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 7)
    - Reference - Attn. Gen. Candidates, Levin, Farley, Hicks, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 8)
    - Reference - William C. Battle, Campaign Materials, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 9)
    - Reference - William C. Battle, Campaign Strategy, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 10)
    - Reference - William C. Battle, Misc. Data, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 11)
    - Reference - William C. Battle ("Jack" Etheridge Land Deals), February-July, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 12)
    - Reference - William C. Battle, Position Papers, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 13)
    - Reference - William C. Battle, Press Releases, June 1968 - June 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 14)
    - Reference - William C. Battle, SIR Poll Incident, June - August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 15)
    - Reference - Black Community in Hampton, Newport News (Source -B. R. Puryear), 1968 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 16)
    - Reference - Chamber of Commerce Addresses, 1969 (Box-folder Box 69 Folder 17)
    - Reference - Comptroller, Report of, 1968 (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 1)
    - Reference - Conventions in Virginia (List), 1969 (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 2)
    - Reference - "The Democratic Party in Va.,1968" - Paul Noble (Report to National Democratic Committee), 1969 (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 3)
    - Reference - Dickenson Co. Loyalty Oath (Vanover and Akers V. Maloney), July 1969 (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 4)
    - Reference - Election Laws and Regulations, 1969 (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 5)
    - Reference - Federal Aid to the States, 1969 (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 6)
    - Reference - Federal Outlays in Virginia - Fiscal Year 1968 (First Half) - I, 1969 (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 7)
    - Reference - Federal Outlays in Virginia - Fiscal Year 1968 (First Half) - II, 1969 (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 8)
    - Reference - Federal Outlays in Virginia - Fiscal Year 1968 (First Half) - III, 1969 (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 9)
    - Reference - Federal Outlays in Virginia, 1968 - Part I (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 10)
    - Reference - Federal Outlays in Virginia, 1968 - Part II (Box-folder Box 70 Folder 11)
    - Reference - Federal Outlays in Virginia, 1968 - Part III (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 1)
    - Reference - Food Programs - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 2)
    - Reference - T. Marshall Hahn (President of Virginia Tech, Potential Democratic Candidate), 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 3)
    - Reference - Highways (Traffic Report - Va. Dept. of Highways, 1967) (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 4)
    - Reference - Linwood Holton, 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 5)
    - Reference - Industrial Safety, 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 6)
    - Industry and Labor, Virginia Publications re: 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 7)
    - Issues Listed by Participants at Charlottesville Meeting, February 1, 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 8)
    - Reference - L.E.A.A. Funds, Virginia Application for, June 10, 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 9)
    - Reference - Manufacturing Plants in Virginia (Division of Industrial Development), January 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 10)
    - Reference - Maps (First District), 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 11)
    - Reference - Maps (Third District), 1969 (Box-folder Box 71 Folder 12)
    - Reference - Maps (Fourth District), 1969 (Box-folder Box 72 Folder 1)
    - Reference - Maps (Fifth District) Pt. 1, 1969 (Box-folder Box 72 Folder 2)
    - Reference - Maps (Fifth District) Pt. 2, 1969 (Box-folder Box 72 Folder 3)
    - Reference - Maps (Sixth District), 1969 (Box-folder Box 72 Folder 4)
    - Reference - Maps (Seventh District) Pt. 1, 1969 (Box-folder Box 72 Folder 5)
    - Reference - Maps (Seventh District) Pt. 2, 1969 (Box-folder Box 72 Folder 6)
    - Reference - Maps (Eighth District less Fairfax Co.) Pt. 1, 1969 (Box-folder Box 72 Folder 7)
    - Reference - Maps (Eighth District less Fairfax Co.) Pt. 2, 1969 (Box-folder Box 72 Folder 8)
    - Reference - Maps (Ninth District) Pt. 1, 1969 (Box-folder Box 72 Folder 9)
    - Reference - Maps (Ninth District) Pt. 2, 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 1)
    - Reference - Maps (Tenth District, including all Fairfax Co.), 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 2)
    - Reference - Miscellaneous Maps, 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 3)
    - Reference - Metropolitan Area Statistics (U.S. Census Bureau), 1967 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 4)
    - Reference - McCarthy Poll, 1968 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 5)
    - Reference - Andrew P. Miller (Democratic Attorney General Candidate), 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 6)
    - Reference - Material re: New Democratic Coalition, 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 7)
    - Reference - Norfolk Local Elections - Misc. Campaign Materials, 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 8)
    - Reference - Statements re: OEO Programs, February-April, 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 9)
    - Reference - Testimony re: OEO Programs, May 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 10)
    - Reference - OEO Programs - Survey of Blacksburg CAP Agendy, April 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 11)
    - Reference - OEO Proposal (Maine), 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 12)
    - Reference - OEO Publications: Legal Services in Action; The Quiet Revolution, 1967 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 13)
    - Reference - Ombudsman Proposal (N.Y. State), 1969 (Box-folder Box 73 Folder 14)
    - Reference - Fred Pollard - Campaign Materials, 1969 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 1)
    - Reference - Fred Pollard - Misc. Data, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 2)
    - Reference - Fred Pollard - Campaign Folder for Pollard Ticket, 1969 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 3)
    - Reference - Fred Pollard - News Releases, April-May, 1969 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 4)
    - Reference - Fred Pollard - News Releases, June-July, 1969 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 5)
    - Reference - Registration and Voting Regulations - Norfolk, 1969 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 6)
    - Reference - J. Sargeant Reynolds - Lt. Governor Candidate, 1969 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 7)
    - Reference - Roanoke (Virginia Town and City), September 1968 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 8)
    - Reference - SCATS Telephone Directory, 1969 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 9)
    - Reference - Taxable Sales (Dept. of Taxation), January-March, 1968 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 10)
    - Reference - Taxable Sales (Dept. of Taxation), April-June, 1968 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 11)
    - Reference - Taxable Sales (Dept. of Taxation), July- September, 1968 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 12)
    - Reference - Taxable Sales (Dept. of Taxation), October- December, 1968 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 13)
    - Reference - Taxes (Reports to Taxation and Finance Subcommittee), 1968 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 14)
    - Reference - U.S. Commission on Civil Rights - "Mobility in the Negro Community," June 1968 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 15)
    - Publication: Report of the (New York State) Public Service Commission, 1965 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 16)
    - Publication: Report of the (New York State) Public Service Commission, 1967 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 16)
    - Publication: Report of the (New York State) Public Service Commission, 1968 (Box-folder Box 74 Folder 16)
    - Reference - Utilities Regulation (Organization Chart of N.Y. Public Service Commission), 1969 (Box-folder Box 75 Folder 1)
    - Reference - Virginia Community Colleges, 1969 (Box-folder Box 75 Folder 2)
    - Reference - Virginia Cooperative Technical Program (Study), May 1968 (Box-folder Box 75 Folder 3)
    - Reference - Virginia Counties:Miscellaneous Materials, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 75 Folder 4)
    - Reference - VEPCO Rates, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 75 Folder 5)
    - Reference - VEPCO Rates: Senate Subcommittee on Inter-government Relations, February 1969 (Box-folder Box 75 Folder 6)
    - Reference - Virginia Jaycees Directory, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 75 Folder 7)
    - Reference - Virginia: Miscellaneous Material, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 1)
    - Reference - Virginia Sales Tax, 1965-1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 2)
    - Reference - Virginia State Government, Organizational Chart, 1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 3)
    - Reference - Voting Statistics (Miscellaneous), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 4)
    - Reference - Washington, D.C., Region (Miscellaneous Material), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 5)
    - Reference - Water Resources (Salem Church Reservoir), 1967 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 6)
    - Reference - Water Resources (U.S. Army Report on James River), 1962 and 1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 7)
    - Reference - Water Resources (Water Resources Development in Virginia - U.S. Army), 1967 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 8)
    - Reference - Zip Codes for Virginia Cities, 1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 9)
    - Reference - Scheduling: Howell Private Schedule (Incomplete), February-August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 10)
    - Scheduling: Howell Calendar, March 21 - July 21, 1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 11)
    - Scheduling: Miscellaneous Howell Calendars, May-August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 12)
    - Scheduling: Rough Drafts of Howell Schedules, 1969 (Box-folder Box 76 Folder 13)
    - Scheduling: Sample Packet - Howell Private Schedule, May 30, 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 1)
    - Scheduling: Memo re: Processing Requests for Personal Appearances, February 28, 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 2)
    - Scheduling: General Correspondence re: Personal Appearances, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 3)
    - Scheduling: Requests for Personal Appearances, May-September, 1968 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 4)
    - Scheduling: Requests for Personal Appearances, October- December, 1968 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 5)
    - Scheduling:Requests for Personal Appearances, January 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 6)
    - Scheduling: Requests for Personal Appearances, February 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 7)
    - Scheduling:Requests for Personal Appearances, March 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 8)
    - Scheduling: Requests for Personal Appearances, April 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 9)
    - Scheduling:Requests for Personal Appearances, May 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 10)
    - Scheduling:Requests for Personal Appearances, June-August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 11)
    - Scheduling: Requests for Appearances (Post-Runoff), February - October, 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 12)
    - Scheduling: Personal Appearances by Substitutes (Durencourt - Sacks; General), 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 13)
    - Scheduling: Betty Howell Personal Appearances, 1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 14)
    - Scheduling: Personal Appearances Cancelled, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 15)
    - Scheduling: Requests for Personal Appearances, Rejected, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 77 Folder 16)
    - Speeches - General Correspondence, February-May, 1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 1)
    - Speeches - Correspondence re: Speech to Virginia Medical Political Action Committee, August-October, 1968 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 2)
    - Speeches - Health Care in Virginia (Material for Speech to Virginia Medical Political Action Committee) - I, 1968 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 3)
    - Speeches - Health Care in Virginia (Material for Speech to Virginia Medical Political Action Committee) - II, 1968 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 4)
    - Speeches - Drafts by Various Writers, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 5)
    - Speeches - Drafts by Jim Burch, May 1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 6)
    - Speeches - Miscellaneous Materials for Drafts, 1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 7)
    - Technique - General, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 8)
    - Technique - Advertising Agencies, Proposals for Howell Campaign, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 9)
    - Technique - Advertising Agencies, Correspondence with Lois Holland Callaway (N.Y.), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 10)
    - Technique - Advertising Agencies, Campaign Proposals by Lois Holland Callaway (N.Y.), 1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 11)
    - Technique - Advertising Agencies, Records of Expenditures by Lois Holland Callaway, 1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 12)
    - Technique - Advertising Agencies, Criticism of Lois Holland Callaway's Howell Media Campaign, 1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 13)
    - Technique - Advertising, Newspapers (Correspondence, Samples), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 14)
    - Technique - Advertising in Periodicals, Programs, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 15)
    - Technique - Advertising in NAACP Program, October-November, 1968 (Box-folder Box 78 Folder 16)
    - Technique - Audio Visual Equipment, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 1)
    - Technique - Billboards: General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 2)
    - Technique - Billboards: Brochures, Directories, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 3)
    - Technique -Billboards: Lists of Signs, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 4)
    - Technique - Billboards: Contracts (Signed and unsigned), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 5)
    - Technique - Billboards: Correspondence with Lois-Holland- Callaway Ad Agency re: Billboards, 1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 6)
    - Technique - "Living Billboards," June 1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 7)
    - Technique - Broadcast Media: FCC Regulations re: Political Campaigns, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 8)
    - Technique - Campaign Song, 1968 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 9)
    - Technique - Canvassing, 1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 10)
    - Technique - Newspapers, Periodicals (Free Use), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 11)
    - Technique - Photography, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 12)
    - Technique - Polling; Results of IRA Poll, May-June, 1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 13)
    - Technique - Radio: Correspondence with Stations re: Political Ads, 1968 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 14)
    - Technique - Radio: Correspondence with Stations re: Political Ads, 1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 15)
    - Technique - Radio: Free Use of News Coverage, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 79 Folder 16)
    - Technique - Radio: Howell Paid Ads, 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 1)
    - Technique - Telephones, Use of, 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 2)
    - Technique - Television: Campaign Film, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 3)
    - Technique - Television: Debates (First Primary), April- July 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 4)
    - Technique - Television: Debates (Runoff), July-August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 5)
    - Technique - Television: Paid Ads, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 6)
    - Technique - Television: Use of News Departments, 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 7)
    - Technique - Television: "T.V. Breakfast with Henry" Program, July 10, 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 8)
    - Volunteers - Miscellaneous Information Cards, 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 9)
    - Volunteers - Forms Filled out at Charlottesville Meeting, February 1, 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 10)
    - Volunteers (Potential) - Names Gathered at Charlottesville Meeting, February 1, 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 11)
    - Volunteers - Norfolk Women for Howell Committee (Correspondence, Roster), 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 12)
    - Volunteers - Senior Citizens for Howell (Background Material by Roger Lidman), 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 13)
    - Volunteer - List of Helpers re: Position Papers, 1969 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 14)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Letters to Virginia Delegates at 1968 Democratic Convention, 1968 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 15)
    - Volunteers - Mccarthy Letters to Virginia Delegates to 1968 Democratic Convention, 1968 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 16)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Letters to Virginia Delegates to 1968 Democratic Convention, 1968 (Box-folder Box 80 Folder 17)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Letters to Virginia Delegates at 1968 Democratic Convention, 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 1)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (Charlottesville), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 2)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (Charlottesville), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 3)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (Newport News), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 4)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (No. Va., Alexandria, Blacksburg, Roanoke), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 5)
    - Volunteers - Mccarthy Petitions (Prince William County; No. Va.), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 6)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (Roanoke), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 7)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (Miscellaneous Virginia), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 8)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (2nd, l0th Districts), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 9)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (4th, 5th Districts), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 10)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (8th, 10th Districts), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 11)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (Miscellaneous Virginia), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 12)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (Miscellaneous Virginia), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 13)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Petitions (Miscellaneous Virginia), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 14)
    - Volunteers - Mccarthy Supporters (Charlottesville), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 15)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Supporters (6th, 7th, 9th Districts), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 16)
    - Volunteers - McCarthy Supporters (Miscellaneous Virginia), 1968 (Box-folder Box 81 Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series K: 1970-1971 General Correspondence
    - January-February, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 1)
    - March 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 2)
    - April 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 3)
    - May 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 4)
    - June-July, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 5)
    - August-December, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 6)
    - Norfolk City Council Races; Correspondence; Campaign Materials, February-July, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 7)
    - Norfolk Federation for Voter Registration; Funding Proposals, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 8)
    - Financial Records, April-August, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, March-April, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 10)